Hello everyone, it's me again, your lovely Molly.
Today, I will continue to share with you about the settings of this model.
Can you hear my voice?
Today, we mainly set the size from the editor to the model.
We also set the movement, posture, transformation, skin change, and other software settings.
First, let's look at the page.
In the page, there is a default editor in the window.
Let's open it.
There are four models here.
The first one is 3D shape.
These models are used to make bags.
If you need them, you can use them to make bags.
At the bottom, there are two female models, two male models, and one female model.
Here, we can see the difference between V1 and V2.
The difference between V1 and V2 is that V1 is a model of 5.0 version.
V2 is a model of 5.0 version.
V2 model is a model of 5.0 version.
V2 model is a model after 5.0 version.
Here, you can choose your model according to the needs you have.
Here, you need to have a screen screen .
If you hear the background noise, it means that I turned the projector off.
Now I turn off the fan.
You can hear the sound of the fan.
Let's continue.
As you can see, there are several models here, one is 6 months old and another is 6 to 18 months old, and another is 7 to 20 years old.
You need to pay attention to the model, our model does not have an action folder, so our model cannot be saved.
In addition to the first 3D shape model, other models also have the corresponding style, shoes, and hair.
You can choose according to your needs.
Next, let's look at the next one.
Now we open a model from the FemaleVR folder.
Then...
Now a model has been opened.
In the main menu, you can see the virtual model option, do you see it?
Click on this option.
Then you will see the virtual model editor option.
Click on this option, you can see a dialogue box.
There are many options to modify the model size.
You can see the height,
you can see the height,
and the size of the whole body and details.
Now let's see the height of the whole body.
This is now defaulted to all height.
All height refers to the height of the whole body except the heel of the model.
The height we usually talk about is the height of the whole body.
Then we click on it now.
There are two hps height and wave height below.
Let's look at the hps height now.
The hps height refers to the height of the model from the point of the shoulder to the ground.
The height of the model from the drive to the ground is also the same.
Then below this is the hps height.
Here, you can choose according to your needs,
so let's get this group to the height first.
This side is the length range
and this is its unit.
Press the button.
Here we see it has an yourself and the Fleet Amap hours,
So you can make your own choices.
Now let's change the data.
We can see that in 3D fashion,
the model's corresponding data will be bright yellow.
This means that there is a corresponding relationship between them.
Now let's change the value.
Let's give it a height of 1.7 meters.
Here we have mm, so we need to write it as 1,700.
Now let's look at the bottom.
Here we have the width.
Here we have the circumference.
The circumference is the length of the chest.
Here we have the lower chest.
The lower chest is the circumference of the model's lower chest.
We choose the circumference of the chest.
Here we set it as 880.
We can see that when we set it to a certain length,
the other lengths will also change.
This is because our system is operating according to tens of thousands of real human data.
So even if some data is not filled in,
the system will adjust the model's size according to the data that has been filled in.
So you don't have to worry about what to do if there is no data filled in.
Next, let's look at the details.
Let's take a look at the details.
Here we have the basics.
The basics are the basic data that everyone uses.
Let's take a look at it.
Let's click on the triangle.
There are two advanced options at the bottom.
The first one is the human body.
This is the human body.
Then there is the second advanced option.
If you are using the Avanon model,
the measurement method of this option is the same as the measurement method of Avanon.
You can use it to change it.
Here you can choose what kind of editing method you want according to your needs.
Then we choose the basics here.
You can also modify its unit next to it,
which is mm, cm and inch.
Now we choose mm, cm and inch.
Let's take a look at the data at the bottom.
We can see that some of the data are gray.
Gray means that the data cannot be modified.
Next, let's take a look at the data at the bottom.
Let's change it to a model.
Let's find its waist.
Let's modify the waist.
The waist is 68 cm.
I'm drooling.
Let's modify its hip.
We can see that there are two types of hip.
Let's modify the lower hip first.
Let's add a colored hip to the lower hip.
Let's modify the upper hip to 88 cm.
Now we have modified the model.
You can see the shape of its body.
After modifying it,
we need to save it.
On the upper right corner,
there are twobelt buttons to save.
Let's click the save button.
We can find the file folder that needs to be saved.
Then...
Enter a name, I will create a new folder and give it a new name
Click Save
Now the model can be saved
If you want to open the model data again,
you can click on the open button next to the save button.
You can open the AVS format file in this folder.
Next, let's see the arrangement.
Here we can see the green and blue points.
The blue point is the arrangement point.
The green point is the arrangement board.
Let's see how to use the arrangement board and the arrangement point.
Open a T-shirt in Gantt.
Open the T-shirt and place it on the arrangement board.
Place it on the front.
Hide the powder line to make it clear.
You can see that
the arrangement board is being wrapped according to the direction of the arrangement board.
Next, let's see this one.
When we click on the arrangement board,
the name of the arrangement board will be selected in the menu.
The name of the arrangement board will also be selected.
However, when I click on the name of the arrangement board,
the arrangement board will show a light.
The name of the arrangement board will be yellow.
It is convenient for us to find the arrangement board.
Next, let's create an arrangement board.
Click on the plus button on the top of the arrangement board.
The new arrangement board will be at the bottom of the model.
You can take a look at it.
You can change the name of the arrangement board below.
You can see that the default name is PEN1.
Add a number to PEN1.
There will be two joints at the bottom.
One is the name of the joint.
The other is the name of the joint.
Add a number to the name of the joint.
Now you can see that the arrangement board automatically runs to the wrist.
There is a height at the bottom.
The height of the arrangement board is the value of the height.
You can adjust it according to your needs.
There are X and Y joints at the bottom.
The X is for the horizontal joints of the arrangement board.
You can see the horizontal joint.
The horizontal joint is pulled.
The Y is the horizontal joint of the arrangement board.
You can adjust the joint number according to your needs.
Go to the arrangement board.
and press the left button on the top of the keyboard.
You can adjust the position of the keyboard by pressing the button on the top of the keyboard.
Now let's place the keyboard on the top of the fingerboard.
Now the keyboard is ready.
However, we can't make the layout of the keyboard.
We need to add a new layout.
Press the Add button on the top of the keyboard.
You will see a new layout.
You can change the name of the layout at the bottom of the keyboard.
Let's change the name of the layout.
You can see that the layout has been added on the top of the keyboard.
There are X and Y values at the bottom of the keyboard.
X means X.
Y means Y.
And Y means Y.
The X value is the size of the layout.
You can turn to the side to see more clearly.
There is a direction in the layout.
The direction of the layout means
It's the direction of the virtual model wrapped around the board.
You can set it according to your own needs.
Let's click on the Arrangement tab and Arrangement point to save.
We found the folder.
Then we first go to the folder.
Click on Save and enter its name.
You can see the file name here.
Click on Save.
You can also save the Arrangement point.
We found the folder we just added.
Enter its name.
You can see its type is ARR.
After saving, click on the Open button.
You can find the Arrangement tab here.
Click on Open.
The Arrangement point is also the same.
Now let's arrange a board on this Arrangement point.
You can see this board is wrapped around the shape of the Arrangement board we just arranged.
This is our virtual model editor.
Next, let's see how to adjust the virtual model posture.
Turn off this.
Then let's delete this layer.
Turn on the
Selection window from the menu.
88.
Then shoot a short shot of us opening this virtual model appropriate to the properties of the software.
You can also do some other poses as well.
Let's see how we can do some other poses.
First, rotate the mouse to the 3D window,
which is on the virtual model.
Then click to display the X-Rite connection point.
Press the X key to add an X.
Now we can see the skeleton point.
On the side, we can see that
the first one is to display the IP address,
which is open by default.
We can see that there are green dots here.
These dots are for waiting.
When we turn it off,
the waiting points will be hidden.
It's not that easy to find them.
So this is open by default.
Now let's click on one of the keys.
Let's click on the key.
A locator will pop up.
This locator has been changed to
the horizontal locator.
Then,
let's rotate the mouse to see how it works.
There is a square button next to it.
If you want to change it,
just press the square button.
Then rotate the mouse again.
We can see that
it has been changed to the horizontal locator.
If you need it,
just press the square button.
If you don't need it,
you don't need to press the square button.
Next to it,
we can see that
the second one is called
the formate joint.
I'm sorry,
I said it wrong.
Now it's open by default.
Let's move one of the joints.
Let's move the position of the finger.
Turn it off,
and then move it.
We can see that
when we move it,
all the joints in the body
can be moved together.
This is to prevent
the joints from changing shape.
these problems from appearing.
Next,
let's take a look at the others.
Let's take a look at the other one next to it.
It's the edit selection joint.
The first one is the edit all.
Now it's the edit selection.
Let's take a look at it again.
When we move the joint again,
we can see that
all the joints in the body
and the joints that are directly linked
will be edited.
The rest of the joints
are not edited.
Let's take a look at it.
These two joints
can be changed
according to our needs.
Now let's take a look at the other one.
This is the move of the joint point.
This is one of the options.
Let's choose one.
Let's choose one joint.
And lock the points of the movement.
Put the joint
noch to the right.
When we move the joint,
all the other joints
are gone.
This is one of the options
we can see.
It's obvious that
when we turn the animal,
the change of joint is there.
It won't turnicky
with the movement.
A little bit of movement
If we move the vegetable,
the rabbit is unaligned
behind it.
In order to prevent the joints from moving due to the movement of other joints,
we can move them slightly to make the model pose more natural.
But if you want the joints not to move, you can use this function.
Let's take a look.
Let's move it back to its original position.
We're still using this joint.
The last one is the rotation of the joint.
Now we rotate the hand downwards.
Then we rotate the other joints.
Let's see how it works.
Let's rotate the arm.
You can see that the whole hand is rotated.
Let's see how it works.
The arm is rotated downwards.
Let's rotate the other side.
You can see that the arm is rotated along with the movement of the whole arm.
So if you don't want the joints to rotate due to the movement of other joints,
you can use this function.
Now we're going to use this function to make a model.
Let's make a walking model.
We're going to use the joint selection tool.
Let's select the foot.
There are two words, TR on the foot.
It means that the foot is rotated and rotated.
Let's turn it off first.
Let's move the foot.
I'll move its foot first.
I might be moving a little slow.
Everyone will be a little bit worried, okay?
You can press the mouse to change the motion on the keyboard to do that model skin surface with Fulbright.
You can press the mouse to change the work surface with Fulbright.
You see if the movement is changed.
and see if it's deformed
Now let's move these two hands
Put these two hands down
and turn the wrist
Pay attention to this position
Don't make it
like this
like a circle
You can use this function
after the live stream
to make some
designs
and send them to us
We recently started the
submit function
Let's take a look at the
design
Use your time
to make it like this
Save the position
Select the file
Save it as a position
The file format is
POS
Save
Now let's
open a virtual model
from the window
Then
open the file
and click on the position
and click OK
Now you can switch to this position
If you need
you can practice later
This is our position
Now let's open the model
Let's look at the action file
We can see that there is a motion file
We can go to the animation mode
and click OK
There are five actions
We can open one
and click on it
This is a motion file
We can show it
If you want to use
other actions
You can
download it from other platforms
You can download it from other platforms
Let's go back to the model mode
You can go to other channels
Download it
This is also
an Adobe platform
Let's take a look
You can
register your account
on the platform
You can download the file
On the right side
there is a preview
It takes some time
to download
Wait a second
You can see here is an action file.
There are many different actions on this web page.
You can download it by yourself.
You can choose a suitable action.
You can see this action.
You can see here is an action file.
You can download it by yourself.
It's a little bit slow.
You can see it's a little bit slow.
Now it's downloaded.
After it's done, let's click on the role.
Here we need to upload the role.
Go to the software and import this model.
Click on the file.
And let's make a...
Save it as a virtual model
Find a suitable folder
Click on it
Enter the name
We save the type here
Choose obj type or fbs
Only these two
I choose the type
We choose obj
We choose the type
Click OK
Save it for a while
Now the file is ready
If you need it, go to this link
I'm in download
This is the download
Click on the next page
Then click Next.
There will be a circle here.
There will be the corresponding name next to it.
You can also put these circles in the corresponding position.
There is a tutorial on the right.
You can take a look at it yourself.
Then click Next.
You can make a Google account for it.
Now it's previewing.
Please wait a moment.
The website is a bit big.
It's done.
You can preview the model here.
Click Next.
You can see it in the preview on the right side of the entire website.
You can see it now.
That's it.
You can zoom in to see it.
Now you can click Download.
Now you can download the Google account.
Let's go back to our page.
I'm going to put the model of Google that we just downloaded in here.
Let's take a look.
The proportion is the ratio of mm.
Click OK.
It's a bit big.
Wait a moment.
OK, it's downloaded.
Now we're going to put on a dress.
Let's wear a dress on it.
Let's put on a dress like this.
Click the model.
Let's do a model.
It's a bit loud.
If the volume is low,
you can turn the volume of your phone or your computer up.
Now go to the Animation mode.
At here in the Animation mode,
Click on the recording button in the animation mode.
You can start recording the whole set of videos.
It takes some time to record.
Please wait for me.
If you have any questions about this live stream,
please feel free to ask us in the comment section below.
It's a bit slow to record this live stream.
Because our live streams are usually a bit slow.
Please wait for a while, okay?
.
Now we are done with the recording, and we are going to start the recording.
Click on the play button.
As you can see, these are the actions we just downloaded from the platform.
If you need other actions, you can also download them from the platform.
That's it.
Next, let's take a look at when you have a scanned model.
If the model is converted into a virtual model,
there is a transfer file in the virtual model.
We found the object file here.
The most important one is obj.
Here, you can choose the gender of the model you want to convert.
This is a male model.
I want to convert him to a female model.
If you don't know the gender, you can actually enter it.
Let's go to the file manager to see it.
Let's convert him to a male model.
Then click OK.
Let's go to the next step.
Here, we can see the model.
Let's turn off the IK connector.
Let's move the model.
We need to align the angle of our scanned model to the angle of our virtual model.
Change the position of the virtual model to a vertical one.
Let's modify it.
For this, we will copy the size of the circle to the angle of ourannen.
Then change the size of the circle to the angle of our scanned model.
Then give it height.
Give it a 110 height.
Not much.
We will reduce the size to 100.
This is how we get the height.
Let's see the distance between the virtual model and the thumbnail model.
We can move the joints here to make the virtual model and the thumbnail model more harmonious.
We can now switch between the virtual model and the thumbnail model.
Now we can go back to our file manager.
We can name the model.
We can change the name of the model.
We can save the name of the model.
This is how to convert our virtual model into a virtual model.
Let's see the others.
When we have a virtual model, we can change the texture of the model.
We can change the texture of the model.
We can create more texture.
Now let's go back to our file manager.
We can now create a new layer of texture.
When we go back to our file manager,
we can choose to add text to our file manager.
It takes a lot of time to process it.
Here are some pictures that have been processed.
You can show them to everyone.
If you are interested,
you can process it in the PS later.
Our official website has a similar tutorial.
If you are interested,
you can search it for me.
The last thing I want to talk about
is the models of other apps.
If you think that
our models are not enough
for your needs,
and you need to download models from other apps,
you can go to
some 3D apps
and create your own models
or purchase them.
Here I have one.
The model I made
is the model of Daz.
We need to
convert the model into
an obj format
and drag it in.
You need to pay attention to the
size here.
Daz models usually use centimeters.
I have pre-processed this model
so you can choose millimeters.
Just confirm it.
Let me show you.
This is a model of Daz.
There are three models here.
I will show you.
You can go to their website
and create a model
or purchase a model.
Just drag it in
and use it.
Note that
you need to use
the obj format.
Now I am going to
create a model.
You will see
that the model is
a model of Daz.
It is a model of Daz.
You will see
that the model is
a model of Daz
with a model of Daz.
You can see
that the model is
a model of Daz,
and the model is
I will try to use the same video as the previous one.
Oh, right. The content of this live stream is not shared by anyone.
If you want, you can search for the content by yourself.
You can find a model from our store window.
Open a model here.
Open the model and click the model.
Here is the text.
Find the text and put it in the PS.
Draw a frame and drag it in.
Then it will be a draft of the script.
The replay will be released in a few days.
You can display the layout.
You can see the draft.
Do you have any other questions?
What is the format of the new model?
You can save it directly next time.
You can save the model to the OBJ format.
You can use it directly.
I just asked you a question.
I saved it to the OBJ format.
You can use it directly.
Do you have any other questions?
How to import the model in the walkthrough?
When you use it,
the model is into the animation mode and then
There will be an action in Motion Weiter者.
Just Drag and Drop it in.
The main function of Motion.
This function support your excitement.
If you are an outside model, you won't be able to use your movements properly.
Do you have any more questions?
If not, we would like to end this live broadcast here.
下面面还有其他的问题吗? What other questions do you have?
可能我装的拉链可以编辑布袋颜色 I may also use a zipper that I made.
Can you edit the color of the fabric and the color of the zipper?
Oh, you're asking if our 3D zipper can edit the color of the zipper and the zipper.
Two different colors, right?
If this is the case, our 3D zipper can only edit one color for the time being.
The color of the zipper and zipper is the same color.
It can't be edited separately for the time being.
Can the model directly be added to the file column on the right and left?
If you have any questions, please do not share the screen.
If you share the screen, it will delete other people's problems.
If you need to import a new file,
click on the window in the drawing book.
Click on the add button.
You can add a new file.
You can add the new file directly to the window in the drawing book.
Let's take a look.
This is where you can see the model you just added.
The model is 3D printed.
It looks like this,
so you can see the model you just added.
It is the same design, but the model is 3D printed.
Look at the cm, and the cm is different.
This is the same, but the model is 3D printed.
It is the same, but the model is 3D printed.
Thank you.
Someone asked about the coordinates of the 3D window.
You can see the grid at the 3D window.
The two first intersecting points of the grid are the coordinates.
You can't see the playback tomorrow.
Our playback will be released after 7 o'clock.
We'll be back in a few minutes.
If you want to watch the online video, you can wait for our replay, because the internet speed is not very good now.
I will try to upload the video as soon as possible.
I hope you enjoy the video.
If you like it, please subscribe to my channel.
Thank you for watching.
If you like my video, please follow me on Facebook and Twitter.
I will see you in the next video.
Bye.
Do you want me to cut your hair?
饭碗的客厂是什么时候可以商量的? When can we discuss about this?
这个我们商量一下 Let's discuss about this.
这个我们可以抽空商量一下 We can discuss about this when we have time.
现在还有别的问题吗? Do you have any other questions?
如何保存OBJ格式的文件? How to store OBJ files?
你是问我们的软件怎么保存吗? Are you asking how to store our software?
如果是我们的软件的话 If it is our software,
直接在文件,然后在导出有个文件 If it is our software,
直接在文件,然后在导出有个文件 We can store our software.
主播不累。主播为你们讲课。主播不累。 I am not tired. I am not tired. I am not tired. I am not tired.
讲一下大字的技巧。 Let's talk about DAS.
我不讲大字。我们讲可乐。 Let's talk about DAS. I am not going to talk about DAS.
我们请问关于可乐的问题。 Let's talk about the question about the question about the question.
大家还有别的问题吗? Do you have any other questions?
已经49分了。 It's already 49 points.
大家有没有看我上一次的直播呀? Have you watched my last live stream?
大家如何有想要看的可以扫描一下我们iant would like to come and see what I am saying?
我们平目左下角那个
那 Singing
שים
We don't talk about Daz. If you have any questions about Daz, please ask them.
How to make socks?
If you want to make socks, you can do it as long as there is a board.
If you want to create a model, what software do you use?
You can use other 3D software.
If you have your own platform or model, you can ask the company to scan the model for you.
Have you eaten?
Have you eaten half a peach?
Can you make food?
How big is your dream?
It depends on your own creation.
How to sew?
Is there any quick and good technique for sewing?
You can see the details in my previous basic series of live broadcasts.
It talks about the production of folding scissors.
Now, I will explain how to make the shoes.
You need to make a scissor without any leather-like material.
The thickness of this scissor is 8 mm, the width of this scissor is 8 mm.
This scissor needs to be folded.
Do you understand?
What else?
You can import the file you need to import into DXF.
Do you have any other questions?
If you have any other questions, please feel free to ask in the comments.
Can the silk metal reflect with the color?
Yes, it can.
This tool is very useful.
If you want to know more about this tool,
you can check out the video I uploaded last week.
It's about the reflection.
What is T-Pose?
T-Pose is your arm.
If you want to know more, please see my video on T-Pose.
How do I make it look like this?
I will use the metal in this case.
Select the metal and add a color at the bottom.
That's it.
You can use any color you like.
I have a padon color here.
You can make your own choice.
Add a little bit of water and mix it well.
Now we can add the green onion.
Add the green onion.
感觉蛋糕里面都是大佬的 I feel like there are a lot of big eggs in the egg.
我在线上有很多点不知道怎么去叫 I have a lot of questions online that I don't know how to answer.
你是直线点吗 Are you a straight line?
如果你是直线点的话 If you are a straight line,
你在 If you are a straight line,
你在导DXF的时候你就将最后一项网材给勾选上就可以了 you can choose the last line when you are in DXF.
你再提单照我要生气了 If you can make another one, I'm going to be angry.
直线点的话 The first one is to check if the points on your board are straight lines or curved lines.
如果是曲线点的话 If you are a curved line,
你导进来变成了直线点的话 If you are a straight line,
你就可以在导入板片的时候勾选上 You can choose the points when you are in DXF.
最后一项就可以了 That's it.
怎么捏脸 I want a beautiful model.
是我们的菲菲不够美吗 Is our Feifei not beautiful enough?
不够美就给她化个妆 That's super beautiful.
大家还有什么别的问题吗 Do you have any other questions?
没有问题的话我们的直播将会在三分钟之后结束 If there is no problem, our live broadcast will end in about three minutes.
曲线点的话你就 If you have a curved line,
有点单机会有一个优化所有曲线点 If you use a calculator, there is a point of optimization.
曲线点
下回课程讲的是一个关于模块化的一个设置 What is the next course about? The next course is a course about modularization.
大家可以在这个就是在这个我们的模式之下可以模块化 You can do modularization in this model.
好不容易看一次直播又来没有关系我们还要下一次 It's not easy to watch a live broadcast again, it doesn't matter, we have to do it again next time.
大家可以期待一下 Please look forward to it.
下次呢就真的是一个小哥哥来给大家播咯 Next time, it's really a little brother to broadcast for everyone.
没有没有感受的话大家可以感受我们的直播我们的录播 If you don't feel it, you can feel our live broadcast.
我们的录播 I'm sorry.
大家如果没有什么问题的话呢我们在直播还一分钟就要结束了 If you don't have any questions, our live broadcast will be over in one minute.
如果播的话可以在期间以后也就是下周五播播 then it will be over at 7 o'clock in the afternoon.
You can watch it next Friday.
If you don't have any questions, then our live stream will be over soon.
You can watch our live stream on August 14th.
If you need it, you can watch it on August 14th.
That's all for today's live stream.
Have a good weekend.
I hope you can watch our live stream on August 14th.
Thank you.
Have a good weekend.